If I'm not doing well, don't think you will either.
إذا لم أكن بخير ، فلا تعتقد أنك ستفعل ذلك.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
W-Why is it you?
W- لماذا أنت؟
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير
Su Mingyue.
سو مينغوي.
I will never like you.
لن أحبك أبدًا.
My feelings aren't that cheap.
مشاعري ليست رخيصة.
I don't just fall for someone so easily.
أنا لا أسقط فقط لشخص ما بسهولة.
You stole my letter.
لقد سرقت رسالتي.
It only made me more certain of my choice.
لقد جعلني فقط أكثر تأكيدًا من اختياري.
Turns out, from beginning to end, I've only ever loved one person.
تبين ، من البداية إلى النهاية ، لم أحب سوى شخص واحد.
And that's Lin Han.
وهذا لين هان.
And your actions now
وأفعالك الآن
are not only despicable
ليسوا قريبين فقط
but also filthy.
ولكن أيضا قذرة.
They only make people feel disgusted.
إنهم يجعلون الناس يشعرون بالاشمئزاز فقط.
When someone does too many bad things,
عندما يفعل شخص ما الكثير من الأشياء السيئة ،
they become uglier and uglier.
يصبحون قبيحين وأقبياء.
Just like you are now.
تماما مثلك الآن.
Lin Han.
لين.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Let me handle things here.
اسمحوا لي أن أتعامل مع الأشياء هنا.
This matter,
هذا الأمر ،
I want to handle it myself.
أريد أن أتعامل معها بنفسي.
This time,
هذه المرة ،
I won't tolerate it anymore.
لن أتسامح معها بعد الآن.
Lin Han.
لين.
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
I'm warning you,
أنا أحذرك ،
don't come any closer.
لا تقترب.
If you dare touch me,
إذا كنت تجرؤ على لمسني ،
my parents won't let you get away with it.
لا يسمح لك والداي بالابتعاد عنها.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Are you scared already?
هل أنت خائف بالفعل؟
Su Mingyue
سو مينغوي
I'm not like you, Su Mingyue.
أنا لست مثلك ، سو مينغوي.
I will personally report this to the police and testify.
سأقوم شخصيا بالإبلاغ عن هذا إلى الشرطة والشهد.
This won't end peacefully.
هذا لن ينتهي بسلام.
I told you,
أخبرتك،
if you mess with my child,
إذا كنت تعبث مع طفلي ،
I will never let you off easily.
لن أتركك بسهولة.
So what if your parents are officials?
إذن ماذا لو كان والداك مسؤولان؟
If necessary,
إذا لزم الأمر ،
I'll even report your parents.
سأبلغ عن والديك حتى.
She has no chance now.
ليس لديها فرصة الآن.
I've hired the best lawyer.
لقد استأجرت أفضل محام.
You spread rumors and slandered before,
أنت تنشر الشائعات واشتغطت من قبل ،
plus kidnapping and attempted murder.
بالإضافة إلى الاختطاف ومحاولة القتل.
You'd better reflect on your actions in prison.
من الأفضل أن تفكر في أفعالك في السجن.
Ying Huiming
يينغ هويمينغ
Do you really think she's so innocent?
هل تعتقد حقًا أنها بريئة جدًا؟
She's just after your money.
إنها بعد أموالك مباشرة.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I, Ying Huiming, really have nothing else.
أنا ، ying huiming ، حقا ليس لدي شيء آخر.
But I do have money.
لكن لدي المال.
As long as she wants it,
طالما أنها تريد ذلك ،
everything I have is hers.
كل ما لدي هو راتبها.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
do you think there's a next life?
هل تعتقد أن هناك حياة القادمة؟
People who couldn't be together
الناس الذين لا يمكن أن يكونوا معا
will meet again in another time and space.
سوف يجتمع مرة أخرى في وقت ومساحة أخرى.
To make up for regrets.
لتعويض الأسف.
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك
I still think
ما زلت أفكر
all of this is a bit too perfect,
كل هذا مثالي بعض الشيء ،
too unreal.
غير واقعي جدا.
I meant every word I just said.
قصدت كل كلمة قلتها للتو.
Can you give me a chance?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني فرصة؟
I don't want to miss out on you.
لا أريد أن أفتقدك.
Sorry, I still...
آسف ، ما زلت ...
Sorry.
آسف.
Lin Han.
لين.
Why does it suddenly appear in my mind...
لماذا تظهر فجأة في ذهني ...
The scene from my previous life's final moments suddenly resurfaces.
المشهد من لحظات حياتي السابقة الأخيرة تظهر فجأة.
In my previous life...
في حياتي السابقة ...
Ladies and gentlemen,
السيدات والسادة ،
let's welcome the arrival of the new millennium together!
دعونا نرحب بوصول الألفية الجديدة معًا!
I collapsed on the very last night of this year.
لقد انهارت في الليلة الأخيرة من هذا العام.
Nine.
تسعة.
Eight.
ثمانية.
Seven.
سبعة.
Six.
ستة.
Five.
خمسة.
Four.
أربعة.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Two.
اثنين.
One.
واحد.
The year 2000 is here!
عام 2000 هنا!
Happy New Year, everyone!
سنة جديدة سعيدة ، الجميع!
Although in this life,
على الرغم من أن في هذه الحياة ،
fate has already changed,
لقد تغير المصير بالفعل ،
Xiaowan can grow up safe and healthy,
يمكن لـ Xiaowan أن يكبر آمنًا وصحيًا ،
but this life-and-death ordeal...
لكن محنة الحياة والموت هذه ...
Can we really get through it safely?
هل يمكننا حقًا الحصول عليها بأمان؟
Can I truly be at ease...
هل يمكنني حقًا أن أكون مرتاحًا ...
being with Huiming?
أن تكون مع huiming؟
Sorry.
آسف.
Sorry, let me help you pick that up.
آسف ، دعني أساعدك في اختيار ذلك.
It's you.
انها أنت.
In the unseen forces of fate,
في قوات القدر غير المرئية ،
some disasters are hard to escape.
من الصعب الهروب بعض الكوارث.
Right now, everything feels like an illusion.
الآن ، كل شيء يبدو وكأنه وهم.
New Year's Eve.
ليلة رأس السنة الجديدة.
Gala.
حفل.
In the unseen forces of fate,
في قوات القدر غير المرئية ،
destiny is inescapable.
القدر لا مفر منه.
Everything before my eyes is just an illusion.
كل شيء أمام عيني هو مجرد وهم.
So you're saying
لذلك أنت تقول
I'll end up like in my previous life,
سأنتهي كما في حياتي السابقة ،
dying on New Year's Eve?
يموت عشية رأس السنة الجديدة؟
Sister Xiaolin,
أخت شياوولين ،
you're amazing!
أنت مدهش!
The clothes sold at the order fair are a hit all over the country.
الملابس التي يتم بيعها في معرض الطلب هي نجاح في جميع أنحاء البلاد.
Now our factory is truly famous.
الآن مصنعنا مشهور حقًا.
Really?
حقًا؟
Really.
حقًا.
Of course it's true.
بالطبع هذا صحيح.
Mom, if you don't believe me, look.
أمي ، إذا كنت لا تصدقني ، انظر.
I'm telling you, Mom,
أنا أخبرك يا أمي
your reputation is really impressive now.
سمعتك رائعة حقًا الآن.
I'm planning to make you into a genius designer.
أخطط لجعلك مصمم عبقري.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
November 15th.
15 نوفمبر.
Only 45 days left until New Year's Eve.
بقي 45 يومًا فقط حتى ليلة رأس السنة.
When everyone is gathered around you,
عندما يتم جمع الجميع من حولك ،
what will that feel like?
كيف سيشعر هذا؟
It's pretty worth trying.
الأمر يستحق المحاولة.
Mom
أم
What are you thinking about?
ماذا تفكر؟
You look so serious.
تبدين جادة جدا.
You didn't even hear me calling you.
لم تسمعني حتى الاتصال بك.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I was just thinking how amazing our Xiaowan is.
كنت أفكر فقط كم هو مدهش Xiaowan لدينا.
You always have new ideas.
لديك دائما أفكار جديدة.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
If you have any ideas in the future,
إذا كان لديك أي أفكار في المستقبل ،
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
Really?
حقًا؟
Then get ready for my "Super Mom Plan."
ثم استعد لـ "خطة أمي السوبر".
First,
أولاً،
create a new trendy brand in China.
إنشاء علامة تجارية عصرية جديدة في الصين.
Second,
ثانية،
make the brand one of the top in the country.
اجعل العلامة التجارية واحدة من أفضل في البلاد.
turn you into a top designer in China.
حولك إلى مصمم كبير في الصين.
Third,
ثالث،
get featured in major magazines.
احصل على مميز في المجلات الرئيسية.
make you the "Chanel of China."
تجعلك "شانيل الصين".
Then start investing in real estate and stocks.
ثم ابدأ الاستثمار في العقارات والأسهم.
No matter if fate can be changed or not,
بغض النظر عما إذا كان يمكن تغيير المصير أم لا ،
at least before I leave,
على الأقل قبل أن أغادر ،
I want every day for Xiaowan
أريد كل يوم لشياووان
to be happy.
أن تكون سعيدا.
But that's not the most important thing.
لكن هذا ليس أهم شيء.
The most important thing is to leave Xiangshui Village.
أهم شيء هو ترك قرية شيانغشوي.
Head to the big city.
توجه إلى المدينة الكبيرة.
How about going to Shanghai?
ماذا عن الذهاب إلى شنغهاي؟
Lin Han
لين
I officially invite you and Xiaowan to come back to Shanghai with me.
أدعوك رسميًا و Xiaowan للعودة إلى شنغهاي معي.
We'll combine your influence
سنجمع بين تأثيرك
with the production strength of the clothing factory
مع قوة إنتاج مصنع الملابس
to create a brand new fashion label.
لإنشاء علامة أزياء جديدة.
Director Ying
المخرج يينغ
I
أنا
I made this decision
لقد اتخذت هذا القرار
not just because
ليس فقط لأن
I like you
أنا معجب بك
but more because I recognize your abilities
لكن أكثر لأنني أدرك قدراتك
Go ahead, Mom
المضي قدما يا أمي
Mom
أم
Go ahead
تفضل
Let me tell you
دعني أخبرك
Shanghai is a big city
شنغهاي مدينة كبيرة
If you go there
إذا ذهبت إلى هناك
you'll definitely make a name for yourself
بالتأكيد ستصنع اسمًا لنفسك
Trust me
ثق بي
In my previous life, I stayed in Xiangshui Town until I died
في حياتي السابقة ، مكثت في مدينة شيانغشوي حتى ماتت
If I could leave this place
إذا كان بإمكاني مغادرة هذا المكان
maybe I could change my fate
ربما يمكنني تغيير مصيري
Then is it possible
ثم هل هو ممكن
that I could stay with Xiaowan a little longer
يمكنني البقاء مع Xiaowan لفترة أطول قليلاً
Then
ثم
let's pack up
دعنا نحزم
and set off right away
وانطلق على الفور
That's great
هذا رائع
We're going to Shanghai
نحن ذاهبون إلى شنغهاي
Going to Shanghai
الذهاب إلى شنغهاي
Xiaowan
شياوان
Even if there's just a slight chance to spend more time with you
حتى لو كانت هناك فرصة بسيطة لقضاء المزيد من الوقت معك
I'll do everything I can to seize it
سأفعل كل ما بوسعي للاستيلاء عليه
I've never been on a plane before
لم أكن على متن طائرة من قبل
I'm really looking forward to it
أنا أتطلع إليها حقًا
Where do you want to sit
أين تريد الجلوس
See if you want to sit here
معرفة ما إذا كنت تريد الجلوس هنا
As long as I'm next to Mom, it's fine
طالما أنا بجانب أمي ، لا بأس
Then here
ثم هنا
Mom, you sit here
أمي ، تجلس هنا
Uncle, you sit here
العم ، تجلس هنا